DEBORAH NEWBERRY

OBJECTIVE

I am a fourth-year student working towards a BS in Computer Science and Mathematics minor at California Polytechnic State University in San Luis Obispo. I look forward to broadening my knowledge by gaining experience through a summer internship.

EXPERIENCE

[December 2014 – Present]

Amazon.com, San Luis Obispo

Ir. Software Developer, Prime Membership

- Became a primary developer in the deprecation of an old service by implementing an API in a new and more efficient manner (using Java).
- Continue to work with a variety of testing services for unit and integration tests.

[April 2014 – November 2014]

California Polytechnic State University

Network Administration Student Assistant

- Provisioned Aruba Access Points for on-campus housing.
- Used JunOS to configure firewall pinholes to allow traffic from certain sources to destinations within the Cal Poly network.

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Orientation Leader 2013-2015, Mustang Band Orientation Coordinator 2014-2015

- Went through extensive 10 week training courses to learn how to be a productive and accountable leader to both the university and the community.
- Coordinated with Mustang Band leadership and New Student and Transition Programs over summer in 2014 and 2015 to sculpt a unique orientation experience for new students involved in marching band.

Service Committee Chair 2015 – 2016, Kappa Kappa Psi, National Honorary Fraternity for College Band members

Mustang Marching Band Flute Section Leader 2015 - 2016

EDUCATION

[September 2012 – Present]

California Polytechnic State University

- Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, Minor in Mathematics
- Dean's List
- Expected graduation: March 2017
- Proficient languages: Java, C, Swift
- Specific skills: databases, iOS development

[916 799 5953] • [DNEWBERRY16@GMAIL.COM]